var destinations = [{
  name: "Panther Hollow Lake",
  lat: 40.436708,
  lng: -79.947572,
  description: "Kids play hockey here when the water turns to ice",
  question: "Do you feel hollow on the inside ? ",
  trueAnswer: "You just get me sometimes. ",
  falseAnswer: "How could I, birds dress me in the morning. "
}, {
  name: "Forbes Field Outfield Wall",
  lat: 40.441581,
  lng: -79.952815,
  description: "The Pirates used to play here",
  question: "Favorite Pirates player?",
  trueAnswer: "Dock Ellis",
  falseAnswer: "Roberto Celemente"
}, {
  name: "The Manor Theatre",
  lat: 40.437254,
  lng: -79.922665,
  description: "Curated movies with a full bar",
  question: "Friday night at the movies?",
  trueAnswer: "Affirmative!",
  falseAnswer: "Can't wait to see the new Transformers movie"
}, {
  name: "Butterjoint",
  lat: 40.450293,
  lng: -79.950893,
  description: "Amazing cocktails",
  question: "Which do you prefer?",
  trueAnswer: "Gin and Tonic",
  falseAnswer: "Gym and Tan"
}, {
  name: "Schenley Overlook",
  lat: 40.4303280,
  lng: -79.9451363,
  description: "Nice view in the park",
  question: "Spicy?",
  trueAnswer: "I only order 11",
  falseAnswer: "Pass the water"
}, {
  name: "Spice Island Tea House",
  lat: 40.440149,
  lng: -79.955671,
  description: "Malaysian & Thai dishes & exotic tea",
  question: "Who's your favorite spice girl ? ",
  trueAnswer: "Sporty Spice",
  falseAnswer: "Scary Spice"
}, {
  name: "Pitt's Doggin It Oakland",
  lat: 40.439619,
  lng: -79.955886,
  description: "Classic Pittsburgh beer shop",
  question: "Who let the dogs out ? ",
  trueAnswer: "You blame your cousin without any shame.",
  falseAnswer: "You are a good person & admit openly that this song is way outdated."
}, {
  name: "Love Locks on Schenley Bridge",
  lat: 40.441194,
  lng: -79.949155,
  description: "Couples make locks, lock to the bridge, and throw away the key",
  question: "How was your first kiss?",
  trueAnswer: "Dreamy",
  falseAnswer: "I don't kiss and tell"
}, {
  name: "Bloomfield Bridge Tavern",
  lat: 40.463300,
  lng: -79.952306,
  description: "Ballin polish food in a dive bar",
  question: "czy mówisz po polsku?",
  trueAnswer: "Tak",
  falseAnswer: "Nie"
}, {
  name: "Independent Brewing Company",
  lat: 40.437698,
  lng: -79.919305,
  description: "Beers from western PA",
  question: "Beer?",
  trueAnswer: "I only drink IPAs",
  falseAnswer: "No"
}, {
  name: "Avalon Exchange",
  lat: 40.437900,
  lng: -79.920386,
  description: "Second hand clothes",
  question: "Is that your grandma's coat?",
  trueAnswer: "It was 99 cents",
  falseAnswer: "No"
}, {
  name: "Girasole",
  lat: 40.451112,
  lng: -79.934077,
  description: "Family Run Italian Food",
  question: "Dinner out?",
  trueAnswer: "It's a date",
  falseAnswer: "As long as its cheap"
}, {
  name: "Mary Schenley Memorial Fountain",
  lat: 40.441926,
  lng: -79.951218,
  description: "Sculpture in bronze and granite by Victor David Brenner",
  question: "Need to get off campus?",
  trueAnswer: "No time",
  falseAnswer: "I was just in Bloomfield"
}, {
  name: "Prantl's Bakery",
  lat: 40.451801,
  lng: -79.932835,
  description: "Best Burnt Almond Tort",
  question: "Gluten ? ",
  trueAnswer: "Honeeeeeeey please, just one small exception to my diet !",
  falseAnswer: "Do you have any kale smoothies to take to yoga instead ? "
}, {
  name: "KBox Karaoke",
  lat: 40.445874,
  lng: -79.948815,
  description: "Korean style karaoke with private rooms",
  question: "Are you the next Frank Sinatra?",
  trueAnswer: "Yes",
  falseAnswer: "No"
}, {
  name: "Tram's Kitchen",
  lat: 40.465604,
  lng: -79.954634,
  description: "Vietnamese Pho",
  question: "Pho?",
  trueAnswer: "Pha?",
  falseAnswer: "Pho"
}, {
  name: "Mellon Park",
  lat: 40.453107,
  lng: -79.916754,
  description: "Visit the Shakespeare garden",
  question: "To be or not to be?",
  trueAnswer: "to be",
  falseAnswer: "not to be"
}, {
  name: "The Last Billboard",
  lat: 40.460470,
  lng: -79.924885,
  description: "installed text art billboard",
  question: "How do you like your art?",
  trueAnswer: "Big",
  falseAnswer: "Yes"
}, {
  name: "Las Palmas Tacos",
  lat: 40.439027,
  lng: -79.955151,
  description: "Bomb tacos",
  question: "Tacos?",
  trueAnswer: "Definitely",
  falseAnswer: "Yes"
}, {
  name: "Jerry's Records",
  lat: 40.432733,
  lng: -79.923509,
  description: "Lots of vinyl",
  question: "Where do you go to buy needles?",
  trueAnswer: "Radio Shack",
  falseAnswer: "Craft Store"
}, {
  name: "Ritters Diner",
  lat: 40.456649,
  lng: -79.941232,
  description: "24-hour breakfast, get some.",
  question: "Munchies?",
  trueAnswer: "Yes",
  falseAnswer: "No"
}, {
  name: "Espresso a Mano",
  lat: 40.466276,
  lng: -79.965096,
  description: "Great espresso in the heart of Lawrenceville",
  question: "Do you frequent affordable Swedish delis?",
  trueAnswer: "Ja",
  falseAnswer: "No"
}, {
  name: "The Squirrel Hill Cafe",
  lat: 40.438145,
  lng: -79.922685,
  description: "Cheap beer, cheap food, all good",
  question: "What kind of bar are you going to?",
  trueAnswer: "Somewhere where I can drink my PBR and smoke my Spirits",
  falseAnswer: "Going to Will Penn"
}, {
  name: "Pamela's Diner Shadyside",
  lat: 40.451650,
  lng: -79.932610,
  description: "Quintessential Pittsburgh Breakfast",
  question: "Breakfast?",
  trueAnswer: "Mmmm pancakes",
  falseAnswer: "Too early"
}, {
  name: "Constellation Coffee",
  lat: 40.465720,
  lng: -79.955637,
  description: "espresso bar and fine coffee",
  question: "Self Promotion?",
  trueAnswer: "Why didn't you say so?!",
  falseAnswer: "Sell out."
}, {
  name: "Construction Junction",
  lat: 40.449926,
  lng: -79.897890,
  description: "Construction reuse store with everything you could ever need",
  question: "Do you go dumpster diving?",
  trueAnswer: "Everyone's trash is my treasure.",
  falseAnswer: "No I only like shiny things."
}, {
  name: "Sphinx Café",
  lat: 40.438091,
  lng: -79.953672,
  description: "Church turned hookah bar",
  question: "Fumas la cachimba?",
  trueAnswer: "Sí",
  falseAnswer: "Qué"
}, {
  name: "The Church Brew Works",
  lat: 40.462045,
  lng: -79.964428,
  description: "Church turned brewpub",
  question: "How do you like your Jesus?",
  trueAnswer: "In a tuxedo T-shirt",
  falseAnswer: "Baby Jesus"
}, {
  name: "Miss Saigon 88 Cafe",
  lat: 40.451256,
  lng: -79.951433,
  description: "Get the pho",
  question: "Do you like vietnamese noodle soup?",
  trueAnswer: "Yes oh yes I do!",
  falseAnswer: "Please no more!"
}, {
  name: "K & T's Fish and Chicken",
  lat: 40.451898,
  lng: -79.952450,
  description: "All the supplies for a good evening",
  question: "Blunts and Chicken?",
  trueAnswer: "Blunts and Chicken",
  falseAnswer: "Chicken, hold the blunts"
}, {
  name: "Salims Middle Eastern Food",
  lat: 40.452767,
  lng: -79.949492,
  description: "Best hummus in Oakland",
  question: "Pita?",
  trueAnswer: "Hummus",
  falseAnswer: "Babaganoush"
}, {
  name: "Mercurios",
  lat: 40.451523,
  lng: -79.932311,
  description: "Pizza and Gelato",
  question: "Pizza or cheeseburger?",
  trueAnswer: "Pizza",
  falseAnswer: "Cheeseburger"
}, {
  name: "Toadflax Inc",
  lat: 40.451069,
  lng: -79.933621,
  description: "Beautiful flower shop",
  question: "I love the smell of...",
  trueAnswer: "Roses",
  falseAnswer: "Bacon"
}, {
  name: "Mind Cure Records",
  lat: 40.457683,
  lng: -79.965824,
  description: "Great for punk records and imports",
  question: "Simple Plan or The Cure ? ",
  trueAnswer: "Drugged out 60 year olds",
  falseAnswer: "Angsty Teens"
}, {
  name: "Copacetic Comics Company",
  lat: 40.457683,
  lng: -79.965824,
  description: "Learn everything about comics",
  question: "Who watches the watchmen?",
  trueAnswer: "Doctor Manhattan",
  falseAnswer: "I do"
}, {
  name: "Eons Fashion Antique",
  lat: 40.456815,
  lng: -79.929343,
  description: "60s and 70s clothing",
  question: "Grandpa's hand me downs?",
  trueAnswer: "Yes",
  falseAnswer: "No"
}, {
  name: "The Junction Hollow Trail",
  lat: 40.435193,
  lng: -79.949930,
  description: "Scenic bike route",
  question: "Bike",
  trueAnswer: "I just bought some fat tires",
  falseAnswer: "I love my fixie"
}]
